question_data = [{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
                  "question": "Which%20of%20these%20mythological%20creatures%20is%20said%20to%20be%20half-man%20and%20half-horse%3F",
                  "correct_answer": "Centaur",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Minotaur", "Pegasus", "Gorgon"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
                  "question": "In%20Norse%20mythology%2C%20Thor%20once%20dressed%20as%20a%20woman.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
                  "question": "What%20mytological%20creatures%20have%20women%27s%20faces%20and%20vultures%27%20bodies%3F",
                  "correct_answer": "Harpies",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Mermaids", "Nymph", "Lilith"]},
                 {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
                  "question": "In%20most%20traditions%2C%20who%20was%20the%20wife%20of%20Zeus%3F",
                  "correct_answer": "Hera",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Aphrodite", "Athena", "Hestia"]},
                 {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
                  "question": "The%20greek%20god%20Poseidon%20was%20the%20god%20of%20what%3F",
                  "correct_answer": "The%20Sea",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["War", "Sun", "Fire"]},
                 {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
                  "question": "Who%20in%20Greek%20mythology%2C%20who%20led%20the%20Argonauts%20in%20search%20of%20the%20Golden%20Fleece%3F",
                  "correct_answer": "Jason",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Castor", "Daedalus", "Odysseus"]},
                 {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
                  "question": "The%20Nike%20apparel%20and%20footwear%20brand%20takes%20it%27s%20name%20from%20the%20Greek%20goddess%20of%20what%3F",
                  "correct_answer": "Victory",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Courage", "Strength", "Honor"]},
                 {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
                  "question": "In%20Greek%20mythology%2C%20who%20is%20the%20god%20of%20wine%3F",
                  "correct_answer": "Dionysus",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Hephaestus", "Demeter", "Apollo"]},
                 {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
                  "question": "Which%20figure%20from%20Greek%20mythology%20traveled%20to%20the%20underworld%20to%20return%20his%20wife%20Eurydice%20to%20the%20land%20of%20the%20living%3F",
                  "correct_answer": "Orpheus",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["Hercules", "Perseus", "Daedalus"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
                  "question": "According%20to%20Greek%20Mythology%2C%20Zeus%20can%20control%20lightning.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
